Guide to the Lewis L. Delafield, Eugene D. Hawkins and Affiliated Attorneys Records circa 1856-1921 (bulk, 1880s-1910) MS 157
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Boxes labeled D-L (Delafield-Longfellow), 1880s-1914 (bulk 1890s-1908)
  - Subseries I.A. Work Files, 1880s-1914 (bulk 1890s-1908)
    - D & L Box #3, circa 1895-1899 (Offsite-box 1)
      2) Gertrude A. Briggs v. Holmes V. M. Dennis Jr, ca. 1896.
      3) Marie Solon v. William H. Masterson re: estate of Louis Solon, ca. 1897.
      4) Joseph Flynn (infant) by William Flynn, guardian v. Henry G. Friedman, ca. 1895.
      5) Mary Leary v. Byron W. Greene Jr re: estate of Michael Leary, ca. 1897.
      6) Henry Kayser v. Genie H. Rosenfeld et al, Westchester County, ca. 1896.
      7) Isaline Ruel v. Frederick S. Pinkus, re: tuition payment for the Ruel School, ca. 1897.
      8) Garrettson v. Alice Green re: commercial matter, ca. 1895.
      9) Anna Dreyer v. James E. Clonin, Queens County, ca. 1896.
      10) Rudolph S. Barrie v. Isidor F. Webner, ca. 1896-99.
    - D & L Box #4, circa 1895-1896 (Offsite-box 2)
      Holds 4 principal matters:
      1) Charles E. Pearsall v. Harriet F. Van Zandt, Westchester County, ca. 1895-96.
      2) John Porter Shannon v. Margaret C. Pentz et al, ca. 1896.
      3) Agnes Corrigan Flood v. Emily P. Delafield, ca. 1895.
      4) Jacob Wendell Jr v. Warren Electric Company, ca. 1896.
    - D & L Box #5, circa 1895-1898 (Offsite-box 2)
      Holds 12 principal matters:
      1) Provost matter, ca. 1897.
      2) Charles M. Carman v. Roberts & Co, ca. 1898.
      3) Adolf Buxbaum v. Max Novak re: guardianship of Alfred Buxbaum, ca. 1898.
      4) List of National Water Works bondholders.
      5) Amos Shirley matter re: property (bicycle) dispute, ca. 1895.
      6) Arvid Passarge v. William J. Harmon re: trusteeship of Isabel M. Harmon under will of Oliver L. Shepherd, ca. 1895.
      7) Indenture between Frederick C. Doolittle, DeVillo White, & Alexander W. Doolittle, 1897.
      8) Lucy Cogswell release to Harlan W. Whipple, ca. 1898.
      9) Mary Stuart v. Andrew S. Thorp, 1896.
      10) Leach v. Cornell, ca. 1896.
      11) Norman W. Harris et al v. John S. White, ca. 1897.
      l2) James B. Ludlow v. Dorothy H.G. Johnson, Henry Kayser, Genie H. Rosenfeld, Paul S. Bolger, Westchester County, ca. 1896
    - D & L Box #6, circa 1894-1895 (Offsite-box 2)
      1) Mrs. Bailey matters, ca. 1895.
      2) 143 Gates Avenue, Kings County, matters (Randolph S. Barrie), ca. 1895.
      3) George Converse v. Mary Mullen, ca. 1893.
      4) Louis Bauer v. John L. Macauley, Euphemia A. Hawes, et al, ca. 1895.
      5) Francis P. Basset v. Union Railway Company of New York City, ca. 1896.
      6) Lizzie M. Somers and Mary Queen agreement, ca. 1896.
      7) Estate of Edward White, 1895?.
      8) Matter of guardianship of Barrington Wight, ca. 1896.
      9) Edward Harris v. Sidney Mann, Kings County, ca. 1894.
      10) Jones v. Helen C. Bostwick, ca. 1895.
      Also holds various miscellaneous small sets of documents.
    - D & L Box #7, circa 1894-1900 (Offsite-box 3)
      Holds 8 principal matters:
      1) James C.E. d'Esterre v. City of New York, ca. 1900.
      2) John C. Austin and George Mohrmann v. Frank Robinson et al, Kings County, Frederick W. Longfellow guardian ad litem for infant defendent, ca. 1894.
      3) Edward H. Schell v. Francis P. Basset, Harriet A. B. Wight, Barrington Wight, Westchester County, ca. 1895.
      4) Estate of George R. Wight, ca. 1895.
      5) Isabel F. Gardner will, ca. 1895.
      6) Stephen C. Talbot and Lowell Talbot v. William C. Holway, ca. 1896.
      7) John Parson and Arthur B. Leach et al v. City of New York re: financial matter, ca. 1900.
      8) Henry K. Thaw matter, ca. 1897.
      Also holds miscellaneous, small sets of documents.
    - D & L Box #8, circa 1894-1900 (Offsite-box 122)
      Holds 3 principal matters:
      1) Various mortgages and related agreements, at least in part for a "Larchmont property." Names include Lizzie Clarke, Francis P. Basset, and others, ca. 1900.
      2) Helen Bostwick matters re: Clear Creek, ca. 1894.
      3) Herman Hesse v. Union Railway Company of New York, ca. 1895.
      Also, various loose papers on miscellaneous matters.
    - D & L Box #9, circa 1892-1897 (Offsite-box 3)
      1) Hariott A.B. Wight matters (titles, agreements), ca. 1896.
      2) School District No. 1 bonds (towns of Castleton and Middleton [Staten Island?]), ca. 1897.
      3) Petition of Emily S. Caswell for trustee in place of Francis P. Basset, ca. 1892-97.
      4) Estate of Edward Wight, ca. 1897.
      Also several miscellaneous small sets of documents.
    - D & L Box #10, circa 1897-1900 (Offsite-box 3)
      1) Luther D. Garrett v. L.D. Garrett Company, Reporting Department, Alfred M. Best, and R.W. Blake, ca. 1899.
      2) Harry B. Parker, Bernard Bridget and Samuel Rosenthal v. American Electric Vehicle Co., (Charles E. Corrigan matter), ca. 1900.
      3) Maria Ghiglione v. Nathaniel Marsh (supervisor of Southfield, Richmond County) et al, ca. 1897.
      5) Settlement of account of Robert C. Geer re: estate of James Humphrey, ca. 1898.
    - D & L Box #11, circa 1894-1899 (Offsite-box 4)
      4 principal matters:
      1) E.H. Rollins & Sons (corporation) v. Trowbridge, MacDonald & Niver Company, et al (city of Pueblo, Colorado and firm of Winslow, Lanier & Co), re: water funding bonds for Pueblo, Colorado (brought in New York court), ca. 1899.
      2) National Water Works bondholder committee matter, packet of correspondence, ca. 1894-95.
      3) U.S. Casualty Company v. O.J. Gude Company, ca. 1899.
      4) Accounts re: Corry bonds.
    - D & L Box #12, circa 1896-1900 (Offsite-box 4)
      1) Ichabod T. Williams estate, ca. 1899.
      2) Henry W. Solfleisch matter re: bill payments, ca. 1898.
      3) Dissolution of Berkeley Athletic Association, ca. 1899.
      4) National Water Works matter, ca. 1896.
      5) Shannon v. Pentz, Frederick Delafield as receiver, ca. 1896.
      6) William Littauer v. Jane A. Gleason, ca 1896.
      7) Joseph Gordon v. Mary G. Hatie et al, (also involves Luther D. Garrett), ca. 1900.
      Also holds miscellaneous loose documents.
    - D & L Box #13, circa 1896-1899 (Offsite-box 4)
      1) Fremont Wilson v. Nelson Hiss, ca. 1899.
      2) Application of the New York & Brooklyn Railroad Company to the Board of Railroad Commissioners of New York State for certificate under Section 59 of the Railroad Law, ca. 1896.
      3) Emma Moffett Tyng and Thomas Mitchell Tyng and Susan Tyng Homans property matter, Irvington, Westchester County, ca, 1898.
      4) Matter re: Union Mutual Fire Insurance Co of New Jersey, ca. 1898.
      5) Matter of Atlantic Mutual Life Insurance Co, ca. 1899.
      6) Matter of Lincoln Fire Insurance Company application for dissolution, ca. 1899.
      7) Incorporation of Days Work Printing and Publishing Company, involves Luther D. Garrett, ca. 1899.
      8) Rutgers Fire Insurance Company of New York v. Mary Brown et al, ca. 1899.
      9) Andrew Freedman (receiver) v. Colonial Assurance Company, ca. 1898.
      10) Bank of Montreal v. City of New York, ca. 1898.
      Also holds other miscellaneous documents.
    - D & L Box #14, circa 1894-1899 (Offsite-box 5)
      1) Hudson River Gold Mining Company (Charles Roblee involved) matter, ca. 1896.
      2) Probate of will of James Lenihan, ca. 1899.
      3) Charles Cohn & Company and B. Holliday & Company matter, ca. 1899.
      4) Appointment of Henry Haag as guardian for Christian Haag, ca. 1897.
      5) Matter of Winthrop E. Scarritt re: Southfield, Richmond County bonds, ca. 1898.
      6) Jefferson M. Levy v. Robert A. Van Wyck as mayor of New York City, et al.
      7) Central Trust Company of New York v. Richmond and Danville Railroad Company, ca. 1894.
    - D & L Box #15, circa 1897-1899 (Offsite-box 5)
      1) William S. Watson v. Carl S. Petrasch, ca. 1897.
      2) Samuel William Toepfer (infant) by guardian Caroline Catherine Toepfer v. Michael Fitzgerald re: compensation for injuries, ca. 1899.
      3) Thomas Dempsey Jr (infant) by guardian Thomas Francis Dempsey v. George G. Travis, ca. 1899.
      Also holds one miscellaneous document.
    - D & L Box #16, 17, circa 1897-1900, 1911 (Offsite-box 5)
      The box held document bundle number 16, but that bundle also held documents marked as belonging in bundle 17, that is, various matters re: Alvin Manufacturing Company of New Jersey, ca. 1897. Bundle 16 holds 3 principal matters:
      1) Abner J. Haydel agreement with Augustus D. Shepard Jr, ca. 1900.
      2) William Ellison v. Edwin A. Hance and Daniel Risley, re: attempt to vacate order of arrest, ca. 1899.
      3) Randolph S. Barrie re: Ridgefield-Montvale, New Jersey property matter, ca. 1899.
      Also holds a few loose documents and City Club of New York officer documents, ca. 1898, with a 1911 outlier.
    - D & L Box #17, circa 1898 (Offsite-box 5)
      Holds many matters. Few documents are linked together and seems in some disarray. Names seen include: Griffin v. Holbrooke; William B. Dinsmore Jr v. Anna A. Clawson and Benjamin Clawson (Westchester County); Francis P. Basset as sole surviving partner of firm George R. Wight & Co on various matters against various parties; I. Gifford Ladd, William H. McCord & Charles M. Jarvis agreement with Harry A.Ensign; Bonta Manufacturing Company of New Jersey; William B. Clark v. Howard R. Gillespie; Matters concerning Thomas J. Dunn Jr, Agnes M. Dunn, and Private Charles Dunn (who died of wound suffered in the Philippines), 1898.
    - D & L Box #18, circa 1897-1899 (Offsite-box 6)
      The bulk of this bundle relates to Leopold Weil v. Joseph Bermel (Supervisor, Newtown, Queens) re: town/village bonds, ca. 1897. There appears to be other related matters mixed in to that. Also holds various small sets of documents including: packet re: Alvin Manufacturing Co.; Luther G. Garrett mortgage, 1899; and a few other miscellaneous documents.
    - D & L Box #19, circa 1896 (Offsite-box 6)
      Appears to all relate to one matter: Joseph Fahys et al v. Samuel F. Myers, Simon Blumauer, Marcus A. Myers, & Adelaide P. Myers, ca. 1896, and related actions, e.g., Samuel F. Myers v. Marcus A. Myers et al).
    - D & L Box #20, circa 1895-1899 (Offsite-box 6)
      1) Lloyd M. Howell v. Robert Goodchild & Emma Goodchild, ca. 1897.
      2) Francis E. Tyng and Dorothy Edmonds matter, ca. 1898, also Tyng matter with Northern Engineering Company, and with W.I. Lincoln Adams, ca. 1899.
      3) William B. Dinsmore Jr New York City tax matter, ca. 1897.
      4) J. Walter Thompson v. Henry E. Childs, ca. 1895.
      5) Robert Hamilton v. Morton C. Nichols, ca. 1897, and Morton C. Nichols v. William Biddle, ca. 1902.
      6) National Linseed Oil Company v. New York Insulating Paint Company, ca. 1898.
      7) Application of Grover Flint to terminate trust for Annie S. Flint and Grover Flint (Flint v. Walter D. Davidge), ca. 1898.
    - D & L Box #21, circa 1895-1900 (Offsite-box 7)
      Holds 9 principal matters:
      1) Church of St. Mary to Emilie P.A. Deprez (mortgage), ca. 1895.
      2) Henry D. Eaton v. Henry Zeimer, ca. 1895.
      3) William H. Hamilton v. Augustus Denton, et al, Nassau County, ca. 1899.
      4) Randolph S. Barrie matter re: Warshauer & Co, ca. 1895.
      5) H.S. Martindale v. Strankman matter, ca. 1899.
      6) Edward G. Blumer v. Abram Lewis et al.
      7) Helen C. Bostwick estate, ca. 1897.
      8) Emily P. Delafield v. John L. MacCammon, ca. 1896.
      9) Daniel W. Shoyer et al v. Henry Fisher et al, ca. 1900.
      Also holds several small sets of documents.
    - D & L Box #22, circa 1895-1900 (Offsite-box 7)
      Holds 2 principal matters:
      1) Joseph Fahys, Henry F. Cook, & George E. Fahys v. Samuel F. Myers, Marcus A. Myers, & Simon Blumauer, ca. 1900.
      2) Katherine Guild Bowne v. Walter Bowne 2nd, ca. 1900.
      Also holds many small sets of documents on various matters. This bundle holds the executed articles of co-partnership between Frederick P. Delafield and Benjamin A. Gould, Jr., dated August 24, 1895.
    - D & L Box #23, circa 1895-1898 (Offsite-box 7)
      1) Benjamin A. Gould v. Edison Electric Illuminating Company of New York, ca. 1898.
      2) Lucy T. Barrie v. William B. Froeligh, Kings County, ca. 1895.
      3) Luther D. Garrett matter re: bond payments, ca. 1898.
      4) Simon Stone v. Metropolitan Telephone & Telegraph Co.
      Also holds a few miscellaneous documents.
    - D & L Box #24, circa 1893-1900 (Offsite-box 8)
      1) Ellen Berry v. John Behnken, Kings County, ca. 1899.
      2) Charles S. Hopkinson v. Angelica T. Hopkinson re: libel, ca. 1899. 3) William Henry Keegan (infant) v. Charles E. Ring, Kings County, ca. 1900.
      4) Helen C. Bostwick matter, ca. 1898.
      5) George Meyer v. James Wadsworth, Kings County, ca. 1900.
      6) Blueprint of property lots at Alberton (Fort Frances), Canada, 1893.
      7) Various matters re: L.D. Garrett Company, ca. 1900.
      8) Ellen A. Baird et al v. Eighth Avenue Railroad Company re: attorney fees in injury settlement case, ca. 1895.
      Also holds many loose, miscellaneous matters.
    - D & L Box #25, circa 1898-1900 (Offsite-box 8)
      1) Controversy between Charles E. Welles, Herrick & Hicks and Pahud F. Thompson, Tenney & Crawford, ca. 1900.
      2) Ferdinand Brooks v. New York Elevated Railroad Company and Manhattan Railway Company, ca. 1898.
      3) Andrew Freedman (receiver of Lincoln Fire Insurance Company) v. various cases, Westchester County, ca 1900.
      4) William M. Lamb v. J. Kennedy Todd, ca. 1900.
    - D & L Box #26, circa 1900 (Offsite-box 8)
      This bundle holds many miscellaneous cases, too numerous to list. Some names noted include: John Parson v. City of New Rochelle, et al, ca. 1900; Pahud Thompson; Helen. M. Sparrow; Fahys; Tenney; Barrie; Animal Product Company; Abraham Jacobson (infant) v. Maximillian Davidoff.
    - D & L Box #27, circa 1896-1902 (Offsite-box 9)
      Holds 5 principal matters:
      1) Various papers re: Great Northern Railway of Canada equipment bonds, ca. 1902.
      2) People ex rel Michael J. Dady v. William V.B. Bennett (supervisor of Gravesend) et al re: Gravesend bonds, Kings County, ca. 1900.
      3) Pahud F. Thompson et al v. George G. Shepard et al, ca. 1901.
      4) Matter re: Proposition to Trenton Industrial Improvement Company for installing complete dynamo, from Wendell & MacDuffie of New York, ca. 1896.
      5) James C.E. d'Esterre v. City of New York, ca. 1900.
      Much of this bundle relates to the Gravesend bonds. Also holds a couple of miscellaneous matters.
    - D & L Box #28, circa 1898-1902 (Offsite-box 9)
      1) Neversink Electric Light & Power Co. matter (involves H.C. McBraire and Thompson, Tenney & Crawford agreements), ca. 1900.
      2) Frederick P. Delafield et al v. City of Syracuse, ca. 1901.
      3) John Foster estate, New York County, ca. 1898.
      4) Red Bank, NJ, property matter re: Clark Holbrook and Elena D.D. Robinson and Henry P. Robinson, ca. 1902.
      Also holds various miscellaneous matters.
    - D & L Box #29, circa 1897-1902 (Offsite-box 9)
      1) Accounts of Ira B. Bassett as executor re: estate of Francis P. Bassett, New York County, ca. 1897.
      2) Findlay, Fort Wayne & Western matter, ca. 1902.
      3) George P. Fiske v. Daniel F. Lewis, ca. 1901.
      Also holds one miscellaneous matter.
    - D & L Box #30, circa 1898-1900 (Offsite-box 10)
      Holds 4 principa1 matters:
      1) Stockholders of Traders' Fire Insurance Company and L.D. Garrett Company agreement, ca. 1900 (and other Luther Garrett matters).
      2) Andrew Freedman (receiver for Lincoln Fire Insurance Company) v. Charles H. Bellows, et al, ca. 1900.
      3) William R. Paddock (d/b/a Stuart & Paddock) v. Lucien Knapp (Treasurer of Long Island City), Queens County, ca. 1898.
      4) E. Holbrook Cushman v. Manhattan Railway Company.
    - D & L Box #31, circa 1900-1901 (Offsite-box 10)
      1) Matthew S. Moloney v. Charles E. Tilton, et al, ca. 1901.
      2) Henry B. Stevenson (infant) by guardian James C. Stevenson v. Thomas F. McLaughlin, ca. 1900.
      3) Bath (NY) Electric & Gas Light Company matter re: bonds, ca. 1900.
      4) Coxsackie matter re: Upper Hudson Electric Company, ca. 1901.
      5) J.M. Sheehan re: South Shore Gas Company, ca. 1900.
      6) William F. Cotter (infant) by guardian James J. Cotter v. Samuel I. Horowitz et al, ca. 1901.
      7) Patrick Mullaney Jr (infant) by guardian Patrick Mullaney v. John W. Butler, New York City, ca. 1901.
      8) James J. Dackerman (infant) by guardian John Dackerman v. Brookfield Glass Works, Kings County, ca. 1901.
    - D & L Box #32, circa 1901-1907 (Offsite-box 10)
      Holds 6 principal matters:
      1) Estate of William Tilden, ca. 1904.
      2) Will of Allen Boyd Forbes, ca. 1907.
      3) Bostwick matter.
      4) Wakefield Cold Air Transportation/Weston Cold Air Transportation matter, ca. 1904.
      5) Nelke, Philips & Bendix v. W.L. Stow & Co., ca. 1901.
      6) Randolph S. Barrie re: Putnam Ave property, ca. 1902.
      Also holds other miscellaneous matters.
    - D & L Box #32a, circa 1897-1905 (Offsite-box 11)
      1) Hall Signal Company patents & related matters, ca. 1905.
      2) Application of Henry Laut (infant) for appointment of Conrad Laut as guardian, Kings County, ca. 1900.
      3) Long Island City revenue bond matter, ca. 1897.
      4) Charles P. Starke v. Charles E. Pearsall & Sons, ca. 1902.
      Also holds several other miscellaneous matters.
    - D & L Box #33, circa 1900-1903 (Offsite-box 11)
      1) Frank W. Wakefield v. Ira G. Ross and John W. DeKay, ca. 1902.
      2) Frederick P. Delafield & Frederick W. Longfellow (firm of Delafield & Longfellow) v. National Automatic Needle Company, ca. 1903.
      3) Robert S. Minturn v. Blazius Ryer, ca. 1900.
      4) Mary A. Sontag v. Herbert Egerton et al, ca. 1900.
      5) Robert S. Minturn et al (executors of Eliza Theodora Minturn) v. Herbert Egerton, et al, ca. 1900.
    - D & L Box #34, circa 1896-1897 (Offsite-box 11)
      1) Charles E. Pearsall v. Manhattan Supply Company, Rockland County, ca. 1897.
      2) H.C. Bostwick estate matter, ca. 1896.
      3) Alvin Manufacturing Company documents, ca. 1897.
      Also holds several miscellaneous matters.
    - D & L Box #35, circa 1901-1903 (Offsite-box 12)
      This entire bundle consists of documents re: Abner J. Haydel v. Augustus D. Shepard Jr, New York County, ca. 1901-1903.
    - D & L Box #36, circa 1902 (Offsite-box 12)
      The bulk of this bundle concerns the arbitration between Erie Fire Insurance Company and Alfred H. Lewis & Frank B. Frear (firm of Lewis & Frear), New York County, ca. 1902. Also holds documents for several miscellaneous matters, including Randolph Barrie re: 764 Putnam Ave property.
    - D & L Box #37, circa 1895-1904 (Offsite-box 13)
      Holds 13 principal matters:
      1) A.M. Harris re: forming a trust company in Richmond County, NY, ca. 1904.
      2) Tuxedo Electric Light Company agreement with Hudson River Telephone Company, ca. 1902.
      3) Christopher Postera v. Robert Vernon, ca. 1897.
      4) Amie E. Clarke v. Marie A. Grening, ca. 1898.
      5) Charles Clark, L. Vaughan Clark & Miner W. Chaffee agreement, ca. 1903.
      6) Partnership agreement between Pahud F. Thompson, Charles H. Tenney, and Harden L. Crawford (Thompson, Tenney and Crawford), ca. 1902.
      7) Hudson River Power Transmission Company matter, ca. 1901.
      8) Stockholders of Maintenance Company of New Jersey agreement with Louis Heck, Gilbert D. Maxwell, & William P. Martin, and related matters involvng H. Hobert Porter Jr and George H. Wheeler, ca. 1903.
      9) Charles E. Pearsall & Son v. Lavinia Lally, mechanic's lien, ca. 1905.
      10) Tallulah Falls Railway Company matter, ca. 1901.
      11) Agreement between Frederic Earle Calkins, Marie Katherine Calkins, and New York Security and Trust Company, ca. 1903.
      12) Ambrose B. Burbank v. John B. Manning, ca. 1895.
      13) Edward H. Myers and Charles Neukirch v. Clinton P. Paine and Percy B. McLaran, ca. 1896.
    - D & L Box #38, circa 1897-1904 (Offsite-box 12)
      1) Knabe & Company v. Slivinsky, ca. 1904.
      2) William Tilden will, ca. 1900.
      3) Henry Reiner v. Blazius Ryer, mechanic's lien, ca. 1900.
      4) American Oddity Company matters, ca. 1899.
      5) Estate of Francis P. Bassett, ca. 1897.
      6) Eney Grupelli v. Daniel L. Risley, ca. 1900.
      7) Annie R. Criss and Harriet B. Criss property contract with Alice W. Thompson, Orange, New Jersey, ca. 1902.
      8) Daniel L. Risley v. James H. McGregor, ca. 1898.
      9) August Roeders (firm) v. Caledonian Insurance Company of Scotland, ca. 1900.
      10) Luther D. Garrett (and other related) v. Walter H. Jaycox as receiver of the Long Island Mutual Fire Insurance Co., ca. 1900.
    - D & L Box #39, circa 1895-1902 (Offsite-box 13)
      1) Randolph S. Barrie re: 143 Gates Ave, Brooklyn, ca. 1895.
      2) Charles M. Switzer bankruptcy, Southern District of New York, ca. 1901.
      3) Herbert D. Bowen v. Ira A. Shaler and John B. McDonald re: claims because of explosion on January 27, 1902, near subway excavation at 41st Street and Park Avenue, ca. 1902.
      4) Claims against New York Central & Hudson River Railroad Company, ca. 1901.
      5) H.W. Shonnard and Floyd N. Franklin v. P. de Tardy de Montravel, ca. 1900.
      6) Empire State Telephone and Telegraph Company re: stockholders' consent to corporate mortgage, ca. 1902.
    - D & L Box #40, circa 1900-1902 (Offsite-box 13)
      1) American Telephone & Telegraph Company v. Peekskill Lighting & Railroad Company, Westchester County, ca. 1901.
      2) John Wanamaker v. Luther D. Garrett, ca. 1901.
      3) Harvey D. Eaton re: Waterville Electrical matter, ca. 1901.
      4) Luther D. Garrett v. Arthur W. Hunt (the early documents for this matter erroneously refer to Albert, rather than Arthur, W. Hunt), ca. 1901.
      5) Farson, Leach & Co. partnership matter, ca. 1900.
      6) Auburn Gas Light Company (Cayuga County) matter, ca. 1901.
      7) Clark Holbrook will, ca. 1902.
    - D & L Box #41, circa 1900-1902 (Offsite-box 14)
      1) Partnership agreement between Harden L. Crawford, Pahud F. Thompson, and Charles H. Tenney, and related matters, ca. 1902.
      2) Prussian National Insurance matter re: reinsurance claims, ca. 1901; this involves Luther Garrett, as do other miscellaneous matters in this bundle.
      3) Francis B. Lark of London re: bicycle tire patent, ca. 1900.
      4) Alvin Manufacturing Company of New Jersey documents, ca. 1902.
      5) Alexander Murgittroyd v. Ira A. Shaler and John B. McDonald re: claims because of explosion on January 27, 1902, near subway excavation at 41st Street and Park Avenue, ca. 1902.
      6) Immanuel Church incorporation, Westerleigh, Richmond County, ca. 1901.
      7) Long Island City improvement bonds matter.
      Also holds many miscellaneous matters.
    - D & L Box #42, circa 1893-1901 (Offsite-box 14)
      1) Thompson, Tenney & Crawford (TTC) release to Welles, Herrick & Hicks, ca. 1900. This bundle also holds several other matters concerning the bankers TTC, among them re: Detroit Michigan water bonds, Missouri drainage bonds, and Malden Electric Railroad Company, ca. 1900.
      2) Agreement between National Prohibition Park Company and Mary A. Harris, Staten Island, ca. 1896.
      3) Packet of office correspondence, 1895-1901.
      4) Will and codicil (printed) of Benjamin A. Gould (the attorney's father), 1893.
    - D & L Box #43, circa 1900 (Offsite-box 14)